Wiseman Racine prays for the people at the Synagogue's Church of all Nations prayer line.
Under the check and conduct of the Holy Spirit the people fall under the anointing of God.
Every shade of affliction in their lives is dispelled in the name of Jesus Christ.
He continues to stretch his hand and declare the people free.
As wise man Racine continues to pray he encounters this young man -
who just being touched begins to manifest.
Let's see how he was delivered.
Who are you?!
Speak louder! Speak out!
I finished him.
You finished him?
No education.
Nothing.
He lusts after women; women is all he knows.
He loves to party, drink and do drugs; he is finished.
Speak louder!
I need him; don't deliver him.
You need him to do what? Explain!
Porn; he is addicted to women, drugs, just name them.
I just need him, please.
How did you control him?
He thinks he is done smoking, drinking and getting tattoos.
How many?
He has up to seven.
Seven tattoos?
Where are they located?
On his body.
On his body?
Yes.
What's the purpose of these tattoos? Explain!
I gave him the addiction.
Anywhere he sees tattoos, he falls in love with them.
No matter what, he has to get them.
Any tattoos he sees, he has to get them.
He gets tattoos?
Yes.
He wants to get tattoos all over his body.
I need him.
He needs to get more. I need him for a special tattoo he is going to get.
He is going to get a special tattoo for me; don't deliver him.
What special tattoo?
This is just the beginning.
Show me the special tattoo.
He is going to get that one on his back.
He does not have it yet but he is going to get it.
Wings – I am a fallen angel so I have to get my wings to fly back.
He is finished.
How many demonic powers do you have?
How many? Speak louder!
If girls see him, they cannot take their eyes off of him.
He loves to display his tattoos; that is what he gets them for.
When they see him and his tattoos, they cannot resist him.
So, when they see his tattoo, nobody can resist him?
No.
What happened to those people?
You mean the girls?
Yes.
Definitely, he is going to have sex with them.
Even in the clubs, he gets them
and he is going to sleep with every one of them.
That is how we do it.
What have you done to the family?
The family - they are in the confusion.
Confusion?
You can ask the parents; nobody stays with them any longer.
I am the only one who wants to stay with them
and I am even forcing myself to stay with them.
I don't even want to stay with them
because they don't allow me to do the things I want to do -
like going after girls, going to clubs, drinking and smoking.
I miss that life.
Who is this man next to you?
Open your eyes!
I can't open my eyes.
Who is this man on your left?!
I can't.
Sir - you are welcome.
Who is this boy?
He is the last-born in the family.
Your last-born?
I just got him and satan took over the boy.
After two years in university, he ran away.
What can you say about his life, his confession?
Honestly, this boy is finished. He drinks, womanises and takes drugs.
See his arms - and it is all over his body.
I had to catch him to bring him here.
God Almighty has heard my prayers.
Madam - who is this boy?
My last-born.
What can you say about his lifestyle?
There is nothing to write home about him; he is somebody who is finished.
There is no business. In school, he cannot make it and he is very stubborn.
He does not respect his senior ones or even his parents.
Welcome, brother. What can you say about him?
In short, he disgraces everybody in the family; he does not do anything.
He doesn’t respect his senior ones; he ran away from school and quit everything.
He womanises and has tattoos all over his body. He goes clubbing.
It entered his head just like that.
You demon - how did you enter him?
I saw him right from the birth, that he was going to serve my purpose -
confusion, anger, lust, limitation, setback, just name them.
The family is in shambles; there is nothing.
None of the sons can provide anything or even own a car,
not mentioning feeding their parents; they are all broke.
Even their sisters' marriages are rubbish.
Of course, you know who did it.
Who did it?!
You know.
You demon, wicked spirit - Jesus has come to set this man free. In the name of Jesus;
Come out! Out! In the name of Jesus Christ.
Out! You wicked demon.
Fire all over your body - in the name of Jesus.
Fire on these demonic tattoos.
Fire all over your body.
Every demonic power be consumed.
Out! In Jesus Christs' name.
Come out, you demon.
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ. All over your body and your hands.
Fire! Holy Ghost fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Holy Ghost fire in the name of Jesus Christ.
In Jesus' name.
Thank you, Lord.
Stand up!
Come.
What happened to you?
Do you remember what you have said?
Look here. Is it your dad?
Yes and that is my mum and my senior sister.
Jesus has cast out that demon - evil spirit, that caused him to misbehave. He is free.
Please - do not remind him his past. His past is over.
Jesus has set you free. Go and follow Him. In Jesus' name.
Amen.
Thank you, Jesus. I am free.
Thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Jesus. My family is free.
People of God - Emmanuel!
My name is Ben Ezenwata. I am from Imo state, but I reside in Togo with my family.
The people standing with me here are my brothers, sisters and parents -
this is my dad, mum and senior sisters and brothers.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN
was possession of an evil spirit – a fallen angel.
The fallen angel exposed me to various bad habits, such as clubbing,
taking drugs, drinking, smoking and getting tattoos all over my body.
It all started when I was a kid and it has been like that ever since.
It was because of the way I was brought up by my family and relatives around me.
I was not getting that much love and attention,
so I grew up becoming a sadist and emotionalist.
That was my experience.
The devil used that as a medium to get into me and
to get me exposed to various bad habits which I was delivered from by wise man Racine.
You said that you were possessed by a spirit of a fallen angel.
Could you just explain did this demon enter your body? And what was his mission in your life?
The way this demon entered was through my exposure to the internet,
movies, music and so much worldly stuff that happened around me.
These were the mediums it used to get into me.
The way this demon looked was half human, half animal.
Getting into me, it made me to know various bad habits and my upbringings too was not that good.
I was taking various kinds of drugs because that was what the demon compelled me to do.
When it compels you, you do whatever it tells you to do because you are not in control of yourself anymore;
you do whatever the demon tells you to do.
That was how I was exposed to the urge to smoke, lust after women, getting tattoos
and taking all kinds of drugs.
It really damaged me academically and in my family life.
It really damaged all aspects of my life because
nobody wanted to be close to me because of disrespect and various things in my family.
It used my as a medium to get into my family and caused more damage.
You said that this demon would appear to you in a form of a half-human, half-creature.
What were the things it would be telling you to do and how did it appear to you before your deliverance?
The demon appeared to me was when I had taken drugs and listened to music.
When I got high as a result of an overdose, I could stay for days without eating.
I listened to worldly music and through that, they came into contact with me
and told me what to do through a trance when I was high.
What were the type of things these demons were instructing you to do?
The type of stuff it told me to do was to take drugs, go clubbing, be disrespectful and to be idle.
It got to an extent that I was addicted to the internet so much.
I had and addiction to watching porn and nude pictures on the internet.
It used this as a medium to get to me.
It told me to do more of those stuff like masturbation and various bad habits I was being possessed with.
It told me to do more of those stuff and compelled me to get tattoos that would deceive people.
The tattoos were not really what they meant.
When you saw the tattoos, you would think that they were really just tattoos but they were not.
So, these were the kind of stuff the demons were telling me to do when I was in a trance with them.
Our brother is mentioning some tattoos.
For the glory of God - could you just show us on your body the tattoos you are talking about?
You said that specifically these demon used these tattoos as a form of deception,
to deceive people to thinking that they are just ordinary, whereas in actual facts
they were something much more than that - a means of an initiation.
We just want you to show us these tattoos.
We are asking these questions so that we can learn from our brothers' experiences,
and I believe viewers around the world are learning many lessons.
Just explain to us the tattoo that we are seeing here.
The tattoo you are seeing here is the head of Jesus.
It reads "Dieu pardonne moi" - "God forgive me" in French.
This is just a means of letting people out there feel that it is religious, whereas it is not.
It is just a mark the evil spirits are using.
Their agents out there – they are tattooists.
Wherever you see a tattooist and you know it is not just ordinary tattoos,
they are agents who the devil sent out to put these marks on youth.
Whenever you see a youth with a tattoo, he is being marked.
Unless he gets his deliverance from the mark of the devil on him,
he will be tormented throughout his youthful life.
So, this tattoo we are seeing is one of the many on your body that is a camouflage, a deception.
People think it is just a religious icon, but in fact it is a means of an initiation, and a mark from satan.
These various tattoos you are seeing on my body are a camouflage.
There was a special one, a fallen angel; he needed his wings to fly back.
He was saying that in order for him to get those wings, he needed those marks to be on me.
I was going to get the tattoo of wings on my back – very huge wings.
In order for him to get his wings back, he was going to get that through me by placing his mark on my back.
We thank God Almighty for our brother's confession.
We believe that there are many valuable lessons that we are learning from this.
Brother, you were talking about the worldly media that you were engaged in,
for example; using the internet, listening to worldly music, playing video games.
Could you explain to us what were the negative repercussions these were having on your life,
and how was satan using these instruments to really infiltrate your life
and indeed the lives of youth around the world?
The means through which this evil spirit gets into contact with the youth
are through the internet and movies.
It is mostly through the internet.
I got it as a result of going online to do all those kind of things -
to download some music and look at nude pictures.
So many youth out there are being enticed with this;
they get initiated and don't know what comes over them.
They see themselves doing things they did not know they would do.
That is how it takes control over them.
We believe that youth around the world and people here are really listening to our brother.
We thank God Almighty that today he is here in the SCOAN.
Tell us brother, what happened when you came to the SCOAN a couple of weeks ago
and received prayer in the power of the Holy Spirit.
Coming here – you can ask my parents – was against my will.
They had to force me to come here and they even had to force me to start watching Emmanuel TV.
I always felt that there was something about this place that I did not want to be part of.
Finally, I came here on the 29th of September with my parents.
I was not even expecting it.
When we went on the prayer line, wise man Racine touched me
and that was where I blanked out and lost memory.
The next thing I found was me standing up from the ground.
We can see on the screen here how our brother was being delivered last weekend.
Tell us, for the glory of God - ever since your deliverance, just testify; what are the changes in your life.
You said before you were addicted to taking drugs, smoking, drinking alcohol, womanizing,
you were addicted to the internet.
Tell us the changes in your life for the last two weeks, since this deliverance.
It has been fantastic and wonderful because getting out of that life is what I had wanted.
Finally, being free from the evil spirit has been a wonderful and fantastic experience to me
because I see myself doing things I couldn’t do before.
Now, I listen to Gospel music, read the Bible and pray a lot.
I see myself being free from all those things and the urge is gone.
I don’t have lust for women or an urge to smoke or take drugs.
I don’t have the urge to listen to worldly music or even movies or looking at nude pictures.
I am completely free now and born-again. Praise the Lord!
Amen. Let's put our hand together for Jesus Christ for our brother's deliverance.
We thank Jesus Christ. And finally, what is your advice to people around the world,
and especially to young people now, that you are delivered? What is your advice?
My advice goes mainly to the parents.
Parents need to be part and partakers of the upbringing of their children,
not just giving birth to them and then thinking they are OK.
There are things out there right now because the devil uses any means
he can lay his hands on to get people to himself and to get people to darkness.
They use these means as a medium to get a contact to the family
to cause confusion and other terrible things to the family.
My advice goes to parents out there.
They need to be connected to their kids.
They need to know how their kids are doing and go to places that their kids go to.
I would like to thank God that He used this as a medium to touch my family
because you can see us that we are all smiling, we are all happy, but this was not how it was before.
For the past 22 years of my existence, this is not how it had been.
This is the very first time, for the past 22 years of my existence,
that the family has come together, been one and everyone is here, complete.
It is a thing of joy for me because it is something I had been praying for.
I thank God that it has finally been fulfilled in my life.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time.
Our brother said that for the first time in 22 years we can see the family together as one, as a result of
his deliverance. We rejoice with this family.
We have no time to listen to the family members
because we still have so many people waiting to testify.
We just want to encourage this family, now that the deliverance had come to your home;
continue to make the Word of God a standard for your life. And indeed the best is yet to come,
in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Thank you, Jesus.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 15/07/2018